<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text</string>
    <string name="article_title">Article Title</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Article Subtitle</string>
    <string name="article_text">https://www.w3.org/Consortium/contact
        \n Health care costs affect the economy, the federal budget, and virtually every American family’s financial well-being. Health insurance enables children to excel at school, adults to work more productively, and Americans of all ages to live longer, healthier lives.
        \n When I took office, health care costs had risen rapidly for decades, and tens of millions of Americans were uninsured.
        \n Regardless of the political difficulties, I concluded comprehensive reform was necessary.

The result of that effort, the Affordable Care Act (ACA), has made substantial progress in addressing these challenges. Americans can now count on access to health coverage throughout their lives, and the federal government has an array of tools to bring the rise of health care costs under control.
        \n However, the work toward a high-quality,
       affordable, accessible  <i>health care system</i> is not over.

In this Special Communication, I assess the progress the ACA has made toward improving the US health care system and discuss how policy makers can build on that progress in the years ahead. I close with reflections on what my administration’s experience with the ACA can teach about the potential for positive change in health policy in particular and public policy generally.Viki was hired in 1995 by the Nevada State Board of Accountancy as assistant directorPrior
to being hired by the NSBA, Viki was with the Nevada State Board of Pharmacy for four years where
she served as Board Coordinator. In this role, she was responsible for numerous tasks associated with
the Board including regulatory and statutory language writing, board meeting coordination,
renewals, licensing and enforcement. Viki brought her previous experience to improve the efficiency
and operation of the NSBA. After establishing herself with the Board through her work Viki was
promoted to Executive Director in 2003. </string>
</resources>